FROM ME TO YOU
'Kay, I'm heading out now.
- You have lots of fun, okay?
- I can't believe it's
Sawako's first sleepover.
Without Dad... What do I
do in this situation?!
Honey, you don't need to
do anything, she's fine.
Oh, and the yokan gift!
Make sure you give it to them!
Right.
DREAM
Today... I go to my first
sleepover in my whole life.
We'll be staying at Chizu's
house. It'll be her, Ayane and me.
Chizuru.
Got a sec?
Tomorrow...
Morning, Chizu!
Good morning you guys.
Oh, hey!
What is that? Sleepover supplies?!
-, Oh, what's up?
- ... Never mind.
But in exchange, just don't come over
tomorrow or the day after that. Just
don't.
Wait... But why? W- What's up with him?
Huh? Did you make Ryu angry or something?
Damn it!
Stupid Ryu...
Just when I was gonna have us play
games to blow off steam and to cheer up
- Yano-chin too!
- Is there any reason
we can't still do that?
Well, the problem is it's Ryu's game.
So, I was gonna have us go to his house to
play it.
Hey, do you remember if you
maybe did anything to make Ryu mad?
Huh? No way, I mean I did kick him out of
my room kinda abruptly the other day, but
- that's whatever.
- What? But why?
Oh, well... because he almost saw this.
Yup, there it is.
S- So what if he got kicked out?!
He's being a little brat about it!
- She's blaming him.
- Just don't come over
tomorrow or the day after that.
But why? The day after
tomorrow is Ryu's birthday too.
Screw this dumb
present! N-No, I can't do it!
Chizu, let's go over to play games.
He never said you can't come over today,
right? You can make up with him while
we're there. -You should just bring the
birthday present now too. What's the point
of a gift if he's
gonna be mad over it? -Ya...
- Yano-chin, I love you!
- There, there.
Friendship!
The risky go-for-broke strategy!
Well, that's how you are
with girls too, though.
I'm the star today! The
guest of honor, got it?!
I feel awesome! In fact, I'm ready
for my closeup! -You guys are the best!
She can just see my brother on New
Year's like she has each year before.
Also It doesn't matter if they see each
other or not. It's not like I wanted to
force anything.
- That's way too many boys!
- What're you guys doing here?
- What about you? What's going on here?
- This is Joe's consolation party.
- Myyyyy, comrade in heartbreak!
- Oh, well, then that's just perfect!
How 'bout we make it a
joint consolation party.
Yano-chin, s-sorry!
It's no problem.
It's something that I've heard a lot,
when two heartbroken people console each
other at their most vulnerable, love can
often bloom between them. Me and Yano,
- y'know?
- Mine too!
- Today's still okay, isn't it?
- Yeah, but uh...
why don't you guys make
some room so they can join us?
- Sorry about that.
- Pardon the intrusion.
Isn't there at least... one
person with some good news?
Nope. None.
- Uhhhh. Nah.
- That settles that.
Hey! Yano! What made
you two break up anyway?
Oh I've got my reasons.
- What a strange feeling...
- Can I get something to
drink over here guys?
Sleeping over at a friend's house,
Being in a crowded, lively room like this,
everyone talking about their love lives...
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
Anyway, I was wondering what happened the
other day...
Running into... someone that I like. All
of these things have somehow become a part
of my reality.
- Yo Ryu, can we get some more cups?
- Yeah, that place's ramen is awesome!
It's a seafood broth, with a strong flavor
and...
Yeah, sure. I'll grab 'em.
I'm gonna see if I can
help. And give him this also.
- I hope he just loves it!
- Yano, what type of guy do you like best?
I like a mature guy who's
open-minded and not desperate.
Ryu! Are you mad at me?
Am I mad? No.
You sure?
I wouldn't say mad, but...
If you suddenly go and kick me out
like that, even I'd feel a little hurt.
Yeah. My bad.
You should know it wasn't really anything
you did though. I just had something I was
trying to keep secret to
make it a little more fun...
Oh, didn't you need to talk
to me about something Ryu?
I'm all ears.
So? Tell me.
Well, um...
That was totally exhausting. I'm home!
Chii!
Toru! You're back!
That had some power to it! Woah!
You've sure gotten big, haven't you!
Aw man! I had no idea!
- Sorry, my bad!
- You are not sorry, don't lie!
I didn't think you were
supposed to get in 'til tomorrow.
Ah, Well, I got off work early today, so...
Woah. Could that be...
What's up guys? Toru!
Heeey Shota, your
hair sure got long, huh?
- Whoa!
- Step back! No, Kazehaya! I got here first
- so I get to talk to him right now! Jeez...
- W- What the heck?
- Some things haven't changed. I love it!
- So this is the person that Chizu likes...
And what's this, Ryu?
you have girls over! Nice!
Ah, they're Chizuru's fr--
My friends from high school!
They're Sawako and Yano-chin! Come here!
- Not too shabby.
- Nooo! Someone throw Yano
- in a closet or somethiiiing!
- I-it was just a joke!
Well you haven't
changed at all, Chii, huh?
I... I'm wearing my pajama top and jeans...
I couldn't buy a new skirt, but I still
shoulda worn my old one.
What's your deal, Ryu! How come
didn't you tell me about this?!
- Where'd she... what's the matter? Come in.
- Uh, you sure?
Is it okay?
Of course it is!
- Alright, was this all of our luggage?
- Yeah, I carried in the rest.
- Good evening.
Your, uh... girlfriend?
She's my fiancé.
It's nice to meet you.
She's...
- Wha-?!
H- hey! Hey, Chizu! Get a
hold of yourself! Come on!
Oh, this buzz cut kid
is my little brother
Hi, I'm Ryu
And I'm Haruka Katayama.
And...
Can't forget about this one, here.
She's Chizuru Yoshida. I call her Chii.
She's been like a little
sister to me since we were kids.
Hello Chizuru. Pleasure's mine.
Uh... um... I live in the
neighborhood. It's good to meet you too!
Well, I'm not actually family or
anyone important here but I... Yeah!
- Welcome.
- Awww, you're too sweet. Thank you!
Chii, why would you say
something sad like that.
- Ugh They're getting married?
- They're getting married?
They're getting married?
- Come on in.
- Okay.
Ryu.
How about we wrap things up for tonight?
It's been a while since Toru's had family
time, and we wouldn't want to get
in the way Yoshida, you guys too.
Let's head out together, okay?
Ah, Yeah! You're right. We invited
ourselves over at a really important time.
Oops.
Listen up outsiders!
Time for us to scram!
My time as guest of honor's over?!
You're an outsider
too, ya' know, Yoshida.
I know! That's why we're all leaving!
- Thanks for having us!
- See ya!
- See ya 'round.
- Later then! Bye!
Bye!
Chii!
Hey. Be safe.
That's so you. But I live
close by! And I'm strong anyway!
Let's gooooo.
I wonder... Right now... What's
going through Chizu's mind...
Later.
Shota.
Thanks for that. If I'd been the
one to say something back there...
Chizuru would've been upset if she
thought I was tiptoeing around her.
If she got mad at me fine... but
she would've just been hurt.
No matter what happens, you're always
worrying about Yoshida before yourself,
aren't you? It isn't your fault bud,
so don't let it get to you so much.
I'm not really upset or anything, but...
But, I don't know.
I'm... not sure what I felt
in that situation was worry.
I still think it was.
He must really like Yoshida. A whole lot.
There!
- Awesome! Looks like I take the win again!
- We've been playing
cards for 4 hours straight...
So, what'll we do next?
Chi... Uh I~uh...
Hey.
Are... Aaare you okay?
Ah. You mean about Toru.
Oh, that's right. I haven't
congratulated him yet. I totally forgot.
Maybe I'll go and visit him tomorrow.
Afterall, the "big brother" I've always
looked up to's finally getting married!
That's right!
And you're totally
gonna find someone better!
... Crap!
Yeah, that's true. But anyway, sorry
we had to leave Ryu's place so early.
It was supposed to be
Yano-chin's consolation party.
Don't even worry about that~ I
totally forgot about it, Chizu.
Woah, when did it get so
late? Should we get to bed then?
I've had this little
crush for a super long time!
I am still a kid afterall so
there's no way I'm even on his radar.
That's why I've decided I'm
gonna become a real catch!
Once I grow up, you never know, right?
See, the person I like
is his older brother.
Chizu is already up and about.
Did I wake you?
I'm gonna wear a miniskirt!
Maybe it's not that
she woke up super early.
Maybe it's that she wasn't able to sleep.
Isn't this sweatshirt awesome?
It's a hand-me-down from my brother, and
there's a little hole around here, but
it's really comfy.
Uh...
Bye! See you guys at school!
I figured that she'd kick and scream and
start bawling like she usually does. Let
it all out, you know? So at first, I
honestly couldn't tell what was going on
with her~ like if she was
angry or hurt, or what.
Is there something we can do for her?
Right now... I don't think
we can do anything really.
We can't even talk to her.
I mean, we could try, but with
the emotional state she's... uh...
She was so happy talking about
how she was gonna wear a miniskirt.
I couldn't comfort her or cheer
her up. I couldn't do anything.
I couldn't find a single good thing
to say that would help her... Nothing...
I'm the same. So, yeah.
I couldn't find the words
either when it mattered the most.
What are friends... supposed to
do in situations like these?
SANADA
Pops is laughing his head off in there.
I'm like their daughter, but I'm not
actually their daughter. Like his little
sister, but not
actually his little sister.
In the end, we're not related.
This is important quality time they're
spending as a family. What business does
some neighborhood kid have butting in?
A neighborhood kid, huh...
Ryuuuuu, let's have a real battle and if
you don't fight me seriously, then I'm
gonna kill you dead! Owwie!
My head! That really hurt me!
Ryu! It's not good to make a girl cry!
Well now you're feeling
all better aren't you?
Toru! I caught a cool
bug! Look, look, look!
Toru! A bug!
Toru! Loooook!
Why bugs? I have no clue why I
showed affection like that as a kid.
Still...
Cool Chii!
Toru would always smile at me.
He was rarely alone. There was always a
girlfriend around. But none of them seemed
to stick around for all that long.
So, when he dated someone,
I never thought much of it.
That's why I held on to my dream
for so long... to marry Toru one day.
I guess the one who
gets to fulfill my dream...
Won't be me.
Feelings that don't get through.
Tears that overflow.
Next time: "Present"